
{
    "match_on_aliases": ["colors", "color", "colour", "colour"],
    "custom_intro" : [
        "we’re about to splash through the color wheel",
        "we’re hunting greens, blues, and oranges",
        "we’re mixing tints, tones, and shades until the palette sings"
    ],
    "questions":[
    { "question": "Can you say red?", "expected_answer": "red" },
    { "question": "Can you say orange?", "expected_answer": "orange" },
    { "question": "Can you say yellow?", "expected_answer": "yellow" },
    { "question": "Can you say green?", "expected_answer": "green" },
    { "question": "Can you say blue?", "expected_answer": "blue" },
    { "question": "Can you say purple?", "expected_answer": "purple" },
    { "question": "Can you say pink?", "expected_answer": "pink" },
    { "question": "Can you say brown?", "expected_answer": "brown" },
    { "question": "Can you say black?", "expected_answer": "black" },
    { "question": "Can you say white?", "expected_answer": "white" }
    ]
}

